{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947679910717","data":{"timestamp":" 947679910717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947679982053","data":{"timestamp":" 947679982052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947679989972","data":{"timestamp":" 947679989971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947679996020","data":{"timestamp":" 947679996020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680002788","data":{"timestamp":" 947680002788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680018119","data":{"timestamp":" 947680018118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680023635","data":{"timestamp":" 947680023635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680029060","data":{"timestamp":" 947680029060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680037231","data":{"timestamp":" 947680037231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680043856","data":{"timestamp":" 947680043856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f3f19e72-8fdc-49fd-a70b-9935e6d6617c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680054445","data":{"timestamp":" 947680054445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680056611","data":{"timestamp":" 947680056611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680058901","data":{"timestamp":" 947680058901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680061741","data":{"timestamp":" 947680061740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680064430","data":{"timestamp":" 947680064430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680073453","data":{"timestamp":" 947680073453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680075245","data":{"timestamp":" 947680075245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680077972","data":{"timestamp":" 947680077972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680080585","data":{"timestamp":" 947680080585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680082753","data":{"timestamp":" 947680082752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680084090","data":{"timestamp":" 947680084090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680086180","data":{"timestamp":" 947680086180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680087712","data":{"timestamp":" 947680087712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680087874","data":{"timestamp":" 947680087874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680090893","data":{"timestamp":" 947680090893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680097093","data":{"timestamp":" 947680097093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680101295","data":{"timestamp":" 947680101295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680105625","data":{"timestamp":" 947680105625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680119731","data":{"timestamp":" 947680119730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680129159","data":{"timestamp":" 947680129159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680129244","data":{"timestamp":" 947680129244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 60f63038-3dec-436a-87c2-84d982e8a6d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680138840","data":{"timestamp":" 947680138839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680139067","data":{"timestamp":" 947680139067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680140030","data":{"timestamp":" 947680140030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680141304","data":{"timestamp":" 947680141304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680144230","data":{"timestamp":" 947680144230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680145075","data":{"timestamp":" 947680145074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680145393","data":{"timestamp":" 947680145393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680146642","data":{"timestamp":" 947680146642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680150152","data":{"timestamp":" 947680150151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680151153","data":{"timestamp":" 947680151152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680151414","data":{"timestamp":" 947680151413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680152364","data":{"timestamp":" 947680152364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680155268","data":{"timestamp":" 947680155268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680156311","data":{"timestamp":" 947680156310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680156790","data":{"timestamp":" 947680156789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680161369","data":{"timestamp":" 947680161368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680161480","data":{"timestamp":" 947680161480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" d590dd58-b203-468b-8d71-9366c00b7282"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680186730","data":{"timestamp":" 947680186730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680190384","data":{"timestamp":" 947680190384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680192585","data":{"timestamp":" 947680192584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680194699","data":{"timestamp":" 947680194698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680199854","data":{"timestamp":" 947680199853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680204079","data":{"timestamp":" 947680204079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680206436","data":{"timestamp":" 947680206436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680209357","data":{"timestamp":" 947680209357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680219568","data":{"timestamp":" 947680219568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680221483","data":{"timestamp":" 947680221483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680228788","data":{"timestamp":" 947680228788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680238093","data":{"timestamp":" 947680238093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680248473","data":{"timestamp":" 947680248472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680258376","data":{"timestamp":" 947680258376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680262708","data":{"timestamp":" 947680262708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680268770","data":{"timestamp":" 947680268770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680274935","data":{"timestamp":" 947680274935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680278098","data":{"timestamp":" 947680278098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680281998","data":{"timestamp":" 947680281998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680284946","data":{"timestamp":" 947680284945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680287717","data":{"timestamp":" 947680287716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680290209","data":{"timestamp":" 947680290209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680291677","data":{"timestamp":" 947680291677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680304308","data":{"timestamp":" 947680304307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680362262","data":{"timestamp":" 947680362261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 2a013e9e-f602-428d-a34f-fc8244581ac2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680374380","data":{"timestamp":" 947680374380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680376440","data":{"timestamp":" 947680376439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680378042","data":{"timestamp":" 947680378042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680380264","data":{"timestamp":" 947680380263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680381944","data":{"timestamp":" 947680381944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680384029","data":{"timestamp":" 947680384029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680385651","data":{"timestamp":" 947680385651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680387439","data":{"timestamp":" 947680387438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale ndege walikuwa na mkutano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680389845","data":{"timestamp":" 947680389845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680391729","data":{"timestamp":" 947680391728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680393616","data":{"timestamp":" 947680393616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680395409","data":{"timestamp":" 947680395409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680397271","data":{"timestamp":" 947680397271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680399146","data":{"timestamp":" 947680399146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680401249","data":{"timestamp":" 947680401249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680403757","data":{"timestamp":" 947680403757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitaka mfalme kama vile binadamu na wanyama walivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680405500","data":{"timestamp":" 947680405500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680407637","data":{"timestamp":" 947680407636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680409876","data":{"timestamp":" 947680409876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680412296","data":{"timestamp":" 947680412295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESTAHILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680414345","data":{"timestamp":" 947680414345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680416353","data":{"timestamp":" 947680416352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni ndege yupi angestahili kuwa mfalme?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680420005","data":{"timestamp":" 947680420005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680422213","data":{"timestamp":" 947680422212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680424296","data":{"timestamp":" 947680424296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680426799","data":{"timestamp":" 947680426799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680428352","data":{"timestamp":" 947680428352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680430594","data":{"timestamp":" 947680430594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680433417","data":{"timestamp":" 947680433416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680435644","data":{"timestamp":" 947680435644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680437448","data":{"timestamp":" 947680437448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680439579","data":{"timestamp":" 947680439579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680442607","data":{"timestamp":" 947680442607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680444913","data":{"timestamp":" 947680444913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmoja alisema."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680446713","data":{"timestamp":" 947680446713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680448486","data":{"timestamp":" 947680448486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680450507","data":{"timestamp":" 947680450507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680452425","data":{"timestamp":" 947680452425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680455412","data":{"timestamp":" 947680455412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOITANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680457765","data":{"timestamp":" 947680457765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680459558","data":{"timestamp":" 947680459558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680462261","data":{"timestamp":" 947680462260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680464919","data":{"timestamp":" 947680464919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680467718","data":{"timestamp":" 947680467717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680469300","data":{"timestamp":" 947680469300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680472299","data":{"timestamp":" 947680472299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680474374","data":{"timestamp":" 947680474374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La hana taji na anapoitana sauti yake ni ya huzuni sana mwingine alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680477046","data":{"timestamp":" 947680477046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680479710","data":{"timestamp":" 947680479709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680481593","data":{"timestamp":" 947680481593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680483985","data":{"timestamp":" 947680483985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680486400","data":{"timestamp":" 947680486400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680488414","data":{"timestamp":" 947680488414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680491076","data":{"timestamp":" 947680491076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680493061","data":{"timestamp":" 947680493060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680495066","data":{"timestamp":" 947680495065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680497386","data":{"timestamp":" 947680497386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680499240","data":{"timestamp":" 947680499240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680501052","data":{"timestamp":" 947680501052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680504361","data":{"timestamp":" 947680504361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNGURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680506238","data":{"timestamp":" 947680506238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680509044","data":{"timestamp":" 947680509044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680511169","data":{"timestamp":" 947680511169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680514930","data":{"timestamp":" 947680514930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi Mbuni kwa sababu yeye ndiye mkubwa zaidi ya wengine na tena hunguruma kama simba mwingine aliwaelezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680517714","data":{"timestamp":" 947680517714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680520856","data":{"timestamp":" 947680520856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680523183","data":{"timestamp":" 947680523183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680525488","data":{"timestamp":" 947680525488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680527219","data":{"timestamp":" 947680527219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680529686","data":{"timestamp":" 947680529686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680532566","data":{"timestamp":" 947680532565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680534745","data":{"timestamp":" 947680534745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680538773","data":{"timestamp":" 947680538773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfalme wa ndege lazima aweze kuruka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680542185","data":{"timestamp":" 947680542185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680544369","data":{"timestamp":" 947680544369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680546137","data":{"timestamp":" 947680546137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680548400","data":{"timestamp":" 947680548400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680550865","data":{"timestamp":" 947680550864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680553371","data":{"timestamp":" 947680553371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680554854","data":{"timestamp":" 947680554853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680557887","data":{"timestamp":" 947680557887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680559786","data":{"timestamp":" 947680559786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680562327","data":{"timestamp":" 947680562327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680566433","data":{"timestamp":" 947680566431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680568365","data":{"timestamp":" 947680568364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680571213","data":{"timestamp":" 947680571213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680573547","data":{"timestamp":" 947680573547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ni mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680576756","data":{"timestamp":" 947680576756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNARINGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680579115","data":{"timestamp":" 947680579114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680581382","data":{"timestamp":" 947680581382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680583005","data":{"timestamp":" 947680583005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHOVA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680584814","data":{"timestamp":" 947680584814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680586418","data":{"timestamp":" 947680586418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680588613","data":{"timestamp":" 947680588612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISITOSHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680590444","data":{"timestamp":" 947680590444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680592824","data":{"timestamp":" 947680592824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680594512","data":{"timestamp":" 947680594512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680597268","data":{"timestamp":" 947680597268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Isitoshe wewe hata si Mwafrika."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAFRIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680599945","data":{"timestamp":" 947680599944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680601989","data":{"timestamp":" 947680601989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680604156","data":{"timestamp":" 947680604156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680606519","data":{"timestamp":" 947680606518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680608522","data":{"timestamp":" 947680608521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680610078","data":{"timestamp":" 947680610078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680611559","data":{"timestamp":" 947680611559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680613603","data":{"timestamp":" 947680613603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680615847","data":{"timestamp":" 947680615847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASTAHILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680618228","data":{"timestamp":" 947680618228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680620753","data":{"timestamp":" 947680620753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninastahili kuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680623163","data":{"timestamp":" 947680623163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680625050","data":{"timestamp":" 947680625050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680626567","data":{"timestamp":" 947680626566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680628367","data":{"timestamp":" 947680628367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680635684","data":{"timestamp":" 947680635684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680641210","data":{"timestamp":" 947680641210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680643057","data":{"timestamp":" 947680643057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680645065","data":{"timestamp":" 947680645065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680647950","data":{"timestamp":" 947680647950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680650139","data":{"timestamp":" 947680650139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680657161","data":{"timestamp":" 947680657161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wewe huenda kulala jua linapochomoza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680661446","data":{"timestamp":" 947680661446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo hawakuafikiana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680663274","data":{"timestamp":" 947680663274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo hawakuafikiana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680665781","data":{"timestamp":" 947680665781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo hawakuafikiana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUAFIKIANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680668638","data":{"timestamp":" 947680668637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680670539","data":{"timestamp":" 947680670539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680672428","data":{"timestamp":" 947680672428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680675055","data":{"timestamp":" 947680675055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680677182","data":{"timestamp":" 947680677181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680680234","data":{"timestamp":" 947680680234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKAYERUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680682560","data":{"timestamp":" 947680682560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680685341","data":{"timestamp":" 947680685341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680688240","data":{"timestamp":" 947680688240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680691745","data":{"timestamp":" 947680691745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mmoja alipiga kelele Yule atakayeruka juu zaidi atakuwa mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680695417","data":{"timestamp":" 947680695417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680697252","data":{"timestamp":" 947680697252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680699130","data":{"timestamp":" 947680699130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680701395","data":{"timestamp":" 947680701395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680703040","data":{"timestamp":" 947680703040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680705807","data":{"timestamp":" 947680705807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680708585","data":{"timestamp":" 947680708585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKARUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680710954","data":{"timestamp":" 947680710954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680712796","data":{"timestamp":" 947680712796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680715197","data":{"timestamp":" 947680715197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndiyo ndiyo walipiga kelele na wote wakaruka juu juu angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680720995","data":{"timestamp":" 947680720995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680722802","data":{"timestamp":" 947680722802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680725158","data":{"timestamp":" 947680725158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680726865","data":{"timestamp":" 947680726865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680728633","data":{"timestamp":" 947680728633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680730461","data":{"timestamp":" 947680730460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680731800","data":{"timestamp":" 947680731800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680733509","data":{"timestamp":" 947680733509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680735286","data":{"timestamp":" 947680735286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680738090","data":{"timestamp":" 947680738090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680740470","data":{"timestamp":" 947680740470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680742419","data":{"timestamp":" 947680742419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680744365","data":{"timestamp":" 947680744365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680746520","data":{"timestamp":" 947680746520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680750762","data":{"timestamp":" 947680750762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bata Bukini aliruka kwa siku nzima moja kwa moja juu ya milima mirefu zaidi duniani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680753369","data":{"timestamp":" 947680753369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680755155","data":{"timestamp":" 947680755155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680757466","data":{"timestamp":" 947680757466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NKWAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680759637","data":{"timestamp":" 947680759637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680761713","data":{"timestamp":" 947680761713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680763840","data":{"timestamp":" 947680763840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680765708","data":{"timestamp":" 947680765708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680769177","data":{"timestamp":" 947680769177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680773125","data":{"timestamp":" 947680773125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680774891","data":{"timestamp":" 947680774890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680777463","data":{"timestamp":" 947680777463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680779946","data":{"timestamp":" 947680779946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680782110","data":{"timestamp":" 947680782110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680784567","data":{"timestamp":" 947680784567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680787464","data":{"timestamp":" 947680787464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Samaki Tai Nkwazi aliruka kwa siku mbili hadi ndani ya rangi samawati juu ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680791832","data":{"timestamp":" 947680791832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680794589","data":{"timestamp":" 947680794588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680796732","data":{"timestamp":" 947680796732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680798745","data":{"timestamp":" 947680798744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680801028","data":{"timestamp":" 947680801028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEUPE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680803683","data":{"timestamp":" 947680803682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680805714","data":{"timestamp":" 947680805714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680808883","data":{"timestamp":" 947680808883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680810708","data":{"timestamp":" 947680810708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680813524","data":{"timestamp":" 947680813524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680815986","data":{"timestamp":" 947680815986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680818868","data":{"timestamp":" 947680818868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680821383","data":{"timestamp":" 947680821382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680823163","data":{"timestamp":" 947680823163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680825517","data":{"timestamp":" 947680825517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680827211","data":{"timestamp":" 947680827211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680829561","data":{"timestamp":" 947680829560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUELEKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680831951","data":{"timestamp":" 947680831950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680833757","data":{"timestamp":" 947680833757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Tai mwenye mgongo mweupe aliruka juu angani kwa siku tatu bila kusimama moja kwa moja kuelekea kwenye jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680839016","data":{"timestamp":" 947680839016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680840976","data":{"timestamp":" 947680840975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680842559","data":{"timestamp":" 947680842559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680845101","data":{"timestamp":" 947680845101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680846905","data":{"timestamp":" 947680846905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680847184","data":{"timestamp":" 947680847184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680850427","data":{"timestamp":" 947680850427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680852438","data":{"timestamp":" 947680852437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680857517","data":{"timestamp":" 947680857517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680859830","data":{"timestamp":" 947680859830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680862792","data":{"timestamp":" 947680862792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680865864","data":{"timestamp":" 947680865864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680868722","data":{"timestamp":" 947680868722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680870674","data":{"timestamp":" 947680870674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680874178","data":{"timestamp":" 947680874178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu yao ndege walimsikia Tai akipaza sauti akisema Ndimi wa juu zaidi mimi ndiye mfalme."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680879472","data":{"timestamp":" 947680879472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680882059","data":{"timestamp":" 947680882059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680884680","data":{"timestamp":" 947680884680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680886801","data":{"timestamp":" 947680886801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680888473","data":{"timestamp":" 947680888473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680890586","data":{"timestamp":" 947680890586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680892567","data":{"timestamp":" 947680892567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680896185","data":{"timestamp":" 947680896184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alisikia sauti juu yake Tink Tink Tink."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680898918","data":{"timestamp":" 947680898918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680900766","data":{"timestamp":" 947680900766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680903344","data":{"timestamp":" 947680903344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680905583","data":{"timestamp":" 947680905583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680907975","data":{"timestamp":" 947680907975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680909648","data":{"timestamp":" 947680909647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680911774","data":{"timestamp":" 947680911774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680914983","data":{"timestamp":" 947680914983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680917130","data":{"timestamp":" 947680917130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680919490","data":{"timestamp":" 947680919490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680921957","data":{"timestamp":" 947680921957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680923586","data":{"timestamp":" 947680923586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680926002","data":{"timestamp":" 947680926001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680927793","data":{"timestamp":" 947680927793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCEDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680930322","data":{"timestamp":" 947680930322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juu ya kichwa chake kulikuwa na mmoja wa ndege wale wadogo kwa wote Ncede Neddicky."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NEDDICKY"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680933248","data":{"timestamp":" 947680933247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680935653","data":{"timestamp":" 947680935653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680937812","data":{"timestamp":" 947680937812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680940823","data":{"timestamp":" 947680940823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYOYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680943087","data":{"timestamp":" 947680943086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680944987","data":{"timestamp":" 947680944987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680946727","data":{"timestamp":" 947680946727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680948827","data":{"timestamp":" 947680948826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa ameshikilia kwenye unyoya mmoja mkubwa wa Tai."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680955177","data":{"timestamp":" 947680955177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUTANISHINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680957157","data":{"timestamp":" 947680957157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680959366","data":{"timestamp":" 947680959366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680961507","data":{"timestamp":" 947680961507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680963171","data":{"timestamp":" 947680963170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680966030","data":{"timestamp":" 947680966029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680966192","data":{"timestamp":" 947680966192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680970331","data":{"timestamp":" 947680970331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680972682","data":{"timestamp":" 947680972682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680975183","data":{"timestamp":" 947680975183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hutanishinda tena Tai alisema na kisha akapaa juu zaidi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680977459","data":{"timestamp":" 947680977459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680980296","data":{"timestamp":" 947680980296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680982876","data":{"timestamp":" 947680982876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680986075","data":{"timestamp":" 947680986075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680988677","data":{"timestamp":" 947680988677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680990668","data":{"timestamp":" 947680990667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliruka juu zaidi ya ndege yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680992652","data":{"timestamp":" 947680992652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680995578","data":{"timestamp":" 947680995578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680999506","data":{"timestamp":" 947680999506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681002142","data":{"timestamp":" 947681002142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681003856","data":{"timestamp":" 947681003855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681006085","data":{"timestamp":" 947681006085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko juu zaidi ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681008183","data":{"timestamp":" 947681008183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681010107","data":{"timestamp":" 947681010107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681012606","data":{"timestamp":" 947681012606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681014344","data":{"timestamp":" 947681014344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681018221","data":{"timestamp":" 947681018221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681020655","data":{"timestamp":" 947681020655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681023127","data":{"timestamp":" 947681023127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ndiye mfalme wenu alisema kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681024629","data":{"timestamp":" 947681024629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" START_LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681026691","data":{"timestamp":" 947681026691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681029018","data":{"timestamp":" 947681029018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681030700","data":{"timestamp":" 947681030700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681032468","data":{"timestamp":" 947681032468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681034648","data":{"timestamp":" 947681034647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681036943","data":{"timestamp":" 947681036943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681038769","data":{"timestamp":" 947681038769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681040360","data":{"timestamp":" 947681040360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681042431","data":{"timestamp":" 947681042430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kutoka chini ya ubawa palitokezea yule ndege mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681044203","data":{"timestamp":" 947681044203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681046074","data":{"timestamp":" 947681046074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681048398","data":{"timestamp":" 947681048398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681050090","data":{"timestamp":" 947681050090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TINK"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681052504","data":{"timestamp":" 947681052504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681054369","data":{"timestamp":" 947681054368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681056702","data":{"timestamp":" 947681056702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681058726","data":{"timestamp":" 947681058726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681060966","data":{"timestamp":" 947681060965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681063137","data":{"timestamp":" 947681063137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFALME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681064882","data":{"timestamp":" 947681064882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndimi mfalme wenu."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681066782","data":{"timestamp":" 947681066782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681070163","data":{"timestamp":" 947681070163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681072395","data":{"timestamp":" 947681072395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681074798","data":{"timestamp":" 947681074798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681076888","data":{"timestamp":" 947681076888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681080047","data":{"timestamp":" 947681080047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681081884","data":{"timestamp":" 947681081884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681083636","data":{"timestamp":" 947681083636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tai alikuwa amechoka hangeweza kuruka zaidi ya hapo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681085717","data":{"timestamp":" 947681085717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681088815","data":{"timestamp":" 947681088815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681091300","data":{"timestamp":" 947681091300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681093292","data":{"timestamp":" 947681093292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681095703","data":{"timestamp":" 947681095703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681098012","data":{"timestamp":" 947681098012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEAMBATANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681099642","data":{"timestamp":" 947681099642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681102094","data":{"timestamp":" 947681102094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCEDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681104765","data":{"timestamp":" 947681104765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alishuka chini akiwa ameambatana na Ncede ubawani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681106941","data":{"timestamp":" 947681106941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681110041","data":{"timestamp":" 947681110041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681112123","data":{"timestamp":" 947681112123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681114336","data":{"timestamp":" 947681114335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681115962","data":{"timestamp":" 947681115962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681118059","data":{"timestamp":" 947681118059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681120194","data":{"timestamp":" 947681120194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681123018","data":{"timestamp":" 947681123017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681124785","data":{"timestamp":" 947681124785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681127490","data":{"timestamp":" 947681127490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wengine walikuwa wameangalia yote haya na walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681132194","data":{"timestamp":" 947681132194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681134569","data":{"timestamp":" 947681134569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681137943","data":{"timestamp":" 947681137942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681139840","data":{"timestamp":" 947681139840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681141720","data":{"timestamp":" 947681141720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681144159","data":{"timestamp":" 947681144159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681146320","data":{"timestamp":" 947681146320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimsubiri tayari kuyang'oa manyoya yake yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681152227","data":{"timestamp":" 947681152227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681154962","data":{"timestamp":" 947681154962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681156734","data":{"timestamp":" 947681156734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681159092","data":{"timestamp":" 947681159092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681161368","data":{"timestamp":" 947681161368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681163410","data":{"timestamp":" 947681163409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEPESI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681165168","data":{"timestamp":" 947681165168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681167172","data":{"timestamp":" 947681167172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681169389","data":{"timestamp":" 947681169389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681172005","data":{"timestamp":" 947681172005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681174236","data":{"timestamp":" 947681174235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681177091","data":{"timestamp":" 947681177091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndege huyu mdogo alikuwa mwepesi wa kujua kwamba walikuwa na hasira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681178912","data":{"timestamp":" 947681178912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681181424","data":{"timestamp":" 947681181424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681183628","data":{"timestamp":" 947681183627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681189076","data":{"timestamp":" 947681189076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681191588","data":{"timestamp":" 947681191588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681194117","data":{"timestamp":" 947681194117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681195700","data":{"timestamp":" 947681195700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681198336","data":{"timestamp":" 947681198336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbilia haraka katika shimo la nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681201459","data":{"timestamp":" 947681201459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681204198","data":{"timestamp":" 947681204198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681206552","data":{"timestamp":" 947681206552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681208980","data":{"timestamp":" 947681208980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681211056","data":{"timestamp":" 947681211056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681213930","data":{"timestamp":" 947681213930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681216110","data":{"timestamp":" 947681216110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULINDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681218927","data":{"timestamp":" 947681218927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681221700","data":{"timestamp":" 947681221700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681229138","data":{"timestamp":" 947681229138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681231779","data":{"timestamp":" 947681231779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMKAMATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681233901","data":{"timestamp":" 947681233901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681235880","data":{"timestamp":" 947681235880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681238426","data":{"timestamp":" 947681238426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681239998","data":{"timestamp":" 947681239997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kuwa na macho makubwa lazima ulinde shimo hili ili umkamate anapotoka nje walimwambia Bundi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681241745","data":{"timestamp":" 947681241745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681243547","data":{"timestamp":" 947681243547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681245578","data":{"timestamp":" 947681245578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681249715","data":{"timestamp":" 947681249715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681251730","data":{"timestamp":" 947681251729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681253606","data":{"timestamp":" 947681253606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681255849","data":{"timestamp":" 947681255848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bundi aliketi mbele ya shimo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681259488","data":{"timestamp":" 947681259488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681261676","data":{"timestamp":" 947681261676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681264768","data":{"timestamp":" 947681264768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681266666","data":{"timestamp":" 947681266665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681268866","data":{"timestamp":" 947681268866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681271287","data":{"timestamp":" 947681271287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681273178","data":{"timestamp":" 947681273178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681275426","data":{"timestamp":" 947681275426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681277644","data":{"timestamp":" 947681277643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681279428","data":{"timestamp":" 947681279428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681281758","data":{"timestamp":" 947681281757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681283309","data":{"timestamp":" 947681283308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681285612","data":{"timestamp":" 947681285612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwa ajili ya joto la jua muda mfupi tu baadaye Bundi alilala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681289163","data":{"timestamp":" 947681289163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681298854","data":{"timestamp":" 947681298853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681301061","data":{"timestamp":" 947681301061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681304608","data":{"timestamp":" 947681304608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUNGULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681312194","data":{"timestamp":" 947681312194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681315289","data":{"timestamp":" 947681315289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681317444","data":{"timestamp":" 947681317444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681323776","data":{"timestamp":" 947681323776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIP"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681327018","data":{"timestamp":" 947681327018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOROKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681328779","data":{"timestamp":" 947681328779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule ndege mdogo alichungulia nje na z-zip alitorokea mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681330763","data":{"timestamp":" 947681330763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681332748","data":{"timestamp":" 947681332748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAIBIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681335534","data":{"timestamp":" 947681335534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681337957","data":{"timestamp":" 947681337956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681341214","data":{"timestamp":" 947681341213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOMZUIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681343803","data":{"timestamp":" 947681343803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681346084","data":{"timestamp":" 947681346084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681353958","data":{"timestamp":" 947681353958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bundi aliaibika mno kwa kutomzuia yule ndege kutoroka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOROKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681356633","data":{"timestamp":" 947681356633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681358630","data":{"timestamp":" 947681358630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681361059","data":{"timestamp":" 947681361059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681363567","data":{"timestamp":" 947681363567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681365188","data":{"timestamp":" 947681365188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa yeye huwinda usiku peke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681367591","data":{"timestamp":" 947681367591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681370311","data":{"timestamp":" 947681370311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681372755","data":{"timestamp":" 947681372755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681375790","data":{"timestamp":" 947681375790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681378466","data":{"timestamp":" 947681378466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681381744","data":{"timestamp":" 947681381744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681384348","data":{"timestamp":" 947681384348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681386005","data":{"timestamp":" 947681386005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681387961","data":{"timestamp":" 947681387960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681390030","data":{"timestamp":" 947681390030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681392041","data":{"timestamp":" 947681392041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681392307","data":{"timestamp":" 947681392307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681401139","data":{"timestamp":" 947681401139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681406872","data":{"timestamp":" 947681406872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" f0e9e08d-40aa-4117-bb82-a6a0dd0deb6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati wa mchana hulala mbali na macho ya ndege wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681433623","data":{"timestamp":" 947681433622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681442637","data":{"timestamp":" 947681442637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681456089","data":{"timestamp":" 947681456089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681460470","data":{"timestamp":" 947681460470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681464372","data":{"timestamp":" 947681464372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681468300","data":{"timestamp":" 947681468300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681470686","data":{"timestamp":" 947681470686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681473815","data":{"timestamp":" 947681473815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681476727","data":{"timestamp":" 947681476727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681479182","data":{"timestamp":" 947681479182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681483530","data":{"timestamp":" 947681483530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681487785","data":{"timestamp":" 947681487784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681490189","data":{"timestamp":" 947681490188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681493475","data":{"timestamp":" 947681493475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681496958","data":{"timestamp":" 947681496958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681498762","data":{"timestamp":" 947681498762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681504961","data":{"timestamp":" 947681504961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681507672","data":{"timestamp":" 947681507672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681511373","data":{"timestamp":" 947681511373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681514307","data":{"timestamp":" 947681514307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681516749","data":{"timestamp":" 947681516748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681518894","data":{"timestamp":" 947681518894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681523039","data":{"timestamp":" 947681523038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681524858","data":{"timestamp":" 947681524858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681527515","data":{"timestamp":" 947681527515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681530026","data":{"timestamp":" 947681530026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681531919","data":{"timestamp":" 947681531919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 24"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681532663","data":{"timestamp":" 947681532663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681537853","data":{"timestamp":" 947681537853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681547302","data":{"timestamp":" 947681547301"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681556100","data":{"timestamp":" 947681556100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681569366","data":{"timestamp":" 947681569366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681584392","data":{"timestamp":" 947681584392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681599615","data":{"timestamp":" 947681599615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681607015","data":{"timestamp":" 947681607014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681615722","data":{"timestamp":" 947681615722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681624663","data":{"timestamp":" 947681624663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681632275","data":{"timestamp":" 947681632275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" e3ef6b4b-10e7-4467-a15a-f1bf969abca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681642872","data":{"timestamp":" 947681642872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681645263","data":{"timestamp":" 947681645262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681646881","data":{"timestamp":" 947681646881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681649637","data":{"timestamp":" 947681649637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681652366","data":{"timestamp":" 947681652366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681655227","data":{"timestamp":" 947681655227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681657368","data":{"timestamp":" 947681657367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681659623","data":{"timestamp":" 947681659623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681662511","data":{"timestamp":" 947681662510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681664891","data":{"timestamp":" 947681664891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681667395","data":{"timestamp":" 947681667395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681670588","data":{"timestamp":" 947681670588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681673038","data":{"timestamp":" 947681673038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681675290","data":{"timestamp":" 947681675290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681677364","data":{"timestamp":" 947681677363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681679316","data":{"timestamp":" 947681679315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681681648","data":{"timestamp":" 947681681648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681687206","data":{"timestamp":" 947681687206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681689870","data":{"timestamp":" 947681689870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681692063","data":{"timestamp":" 947681692063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681695385","data":{"timestamp":" 947681695385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681697146","data":{"timestamp":" 947681697146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681699542","data":{"timestamp":" 947681699542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681701257","data":{"timestamp":" 947681701257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681701460","data":{"timestamp":" 947681701460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681708270","data":{"timestamp":" 947681708270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681710328","data":{"timestamp":" 947681710327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681712362","data":{"timestamp":" 947681712362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681715300","data":{"timestamp":" 947681715300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681717286","data":{"timestamp":" 947681717286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681724863","data":{"timestamp":" 947681724863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681726878","data":{"timestamp":" 947681726878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681729353","data":{"timestamp":" 947681729353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681731751","data":{"timestamp":" 947681731751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681734063","data":{"timestamp":" 947681734063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681735679","data":{"timestamp":" 947681735679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681737531","data":{"timestamp":" 947681737531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681740011","data":{"timestamp":" 947681740011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681742103","data":{"timestamp":" 947681742102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681744386","data":{"timestamp":" 947681744386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681747085","data":{"timestamp":" 947681747085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681749206","data":{"timestamp":" 947681749206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681752072","data":{"timestamp":" 947681752072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681754477","data":{"timestamp":" 947681754477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681756407","data":{"timestamp":" 947681756407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681758221","data":{"timestamp":" 947681758221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681761209","data":{"timestamp":" 947681761209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681763269","data":{"timestamp":" 947681763269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681765007","data":{"timestamp":" 947681765007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681767451","data":{"timestamp":" 947681767451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681769466","data":{"timestamp":" 947681769466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681771612","data":{"timestamp":" 947681771611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681774652","data":{"timestamp":" 947681774652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAZIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681778294","data":{"timestamp":" 947681778294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681780524","data":{"timestamp":" 947681780524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681782989","data":{"timestamp":" 947681782989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681785687","data":{"timestamp":" 947681785687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681788143","data":{"timestamp":" 947681788143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681790826","data":{"timestamp":" 947681790826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681793890","data":{"timestamp":" 947681793890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681798144","data":{"timestamp":" 947681798144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681800448","data":{"timestamp":" 947681800448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681802118","data":{"timestamp":" 947681802118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681804493","data":{"timestamp":" 947681804493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681806517","data":{"timestamp":" 947681806517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681812660","data":{"timestamp":" 947681812660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681815510","data":{"timestamp":" 947681815510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681817429","data":{"timestamp":" 947681817429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681819876","data":{"timestamp":" 947681819876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681822054","data":{"timestamp":" 947681822054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681824387","data":{"timestamp":" 947681824387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681826775","data":{"timestamp":" 947681826775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681828859","data":{"timestamp":" 947681828859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681832408","data":{"timestamp":" 947681832408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681834466","data":{"timestamp":" 947681834466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681837357","data":{"timestamp":" 947681837357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681839477","data":{"timestamp":" 947681839477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHUKUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681841435","data":{"timestamp":" 947681841435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681843836","data":{"timestamp":" 947681843836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681846560","data":{"timestamp":" 947681846560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATENGEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681848330","data":{"timestamp":" 947681848330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681854559","data":{"timestamp":" 947681854559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681856212","data":{"timestamp":" 947681856211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681858369","data":{"timestamp":" 947681858369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681860714","data":{"timestamp":" 947681860713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681863572","data":{"timestamp":" 947681863572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681866242","data":{"timestamp":" 947681866242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681868539","data":{"timestamp":" 947681868538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681870054","data":{"timestamp":" 947681870054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681870262","data":{"timestamp":" 947681870262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681873455","data":{"timestamp":" 947681873454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681875761","data":{"timestamp":" 947681875761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681879488","data":{"timestamp":" 947681879487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPEPERUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681881334","data":{"timestamp":" 947681881334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681884002","data":{"timestamp":" 947681884002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681886325","data":{"timestamp":" 947681886325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681888333","data":{"timestamp":" 947681888332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681888510","data":{"timestamp":" 947681888510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681896861","data":{"timestamp":" 947681896861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681903379","data":{"timestamp":" 947681903378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681910887","data":{"timestamp":" 947681910887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 09163b06-34a1-46c1-9665-84fab269458f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681921008","data":{"timestamp":" 947681921008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681923177","data":{"timestamp":" 947681923177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681924998","data":{"timestamp":" 947681924998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681927334","data":{"timestamp":" 947681927334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681929907","data":{"timestamp":" 947681929907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681933839","data":{"timestamp":" 947681933839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681934447","data":{"timestamp":" 947681934446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681934610","data":{"timestamp":" 947681934609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681941265","data":{"timestamp":" 947681941264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" c40100cc-cc10-4021-acf8-2b42997a60f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681958736","data":{"timestamp":" 947681958736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681960818","data":{"timestamp":" 947681960818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681963001","data":{"timestamp":" 947681963001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681964768","data":{"timestamp":" 947681964768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681967626","data":{"timestamp":" 947681967626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681970700","data":{"timestamp":" 947681970700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681973582","data":{"timestamp":" 947681973581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681976064","data":{"timestamp":" 947681976064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681978560","data":{"timestamp":" 947681978560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681982276","data":{"timestamp":" 947681982276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681984315","data":{"timestamp":" 947681984315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681986555","data":{"timestamp":" 947681986555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681989073","data":{"timestamp":" 947681989073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681991876","data":{"timestamp":" 947681991876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681994310","data":{"timestamp":" 947681994310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681997564","data":{"timestamp":" 947681997563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682000493","data":{"timestamp":" 947682000493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682004785","data":{"timestamp":" 947682004785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682007757","data":{"timestamp":" 947682007756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682012076","data":{"timestamp":" 947682012076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682014698","data":{"timestamp":" 947682014698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682017438","data":{"timestamp":" 947682017438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682019363","data":{"timestamp":" 947682019363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682021415","data":{"timestamp":" 947682021415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682023245","data":{"timestamp":" 947682023245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682028476","data":{"timestamp":" 947682028476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682030554","data":{"timestamp":" 947682030554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682033256","data":{"timestamp":" 947682033255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682035962","data":{"timestamp":" 947682035962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682038042","data":{"timestamp":" 947682038042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682039701","data":{"timestamp":" 947682039701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682042279","data":{"timestamp":" 947682042279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682045828","data":{"timestamp":" 947682045828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682048384","data":{"timestamp":" 947682048383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682050942","data":{"timestamp":" 947682050942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682053720","data":{"timestamp":" 947682053720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682055590","data":{"timestamp":" 947682055590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682058043","data":{"timestamp":" 947682058043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682061266","data":{"timestamp":" 947682061265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682064088","data":{"timestamp":" 947682064088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682066472","data":{"timestamp":" 947682066471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682070161","data":{"timestamp":" 947682070161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682072010","data":{"timestamp":" 947682072010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682073996","data":{"timestamp":" 947682073996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682077669","data":{"timestamp":" 947682077668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682080056","data":{"timestamp":" 947682080056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682082546","data":{"timestamp":" 947682082546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682085077","data":{"timestamp":" 947682085077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682088305","data":{"timestamp":" 947682088305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682090966","data":{"timestamp":" 947682090966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682093336","data":{"timestamp":" 947682093336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682096910","data":{"timestamp":" 947682096909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682099358","data":{"timestamp":" 947682099358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682102672","data":{"timestamp":" 947682102672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682105246","data":{"timestamp":" 947682105246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682107941","data":{"timestamp":" 947682107941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682109521","data":{"timestamp":" 947682109521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682112320","data":{"timestamp":" 947682112320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682114895","data":{"timestamp":" 947682114895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682117311","data":{"timestamp":" 947682117310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682120862","data":{"timestamp":" 947682120861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682123896","data":{"timestamp":" 947682123896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682126562","data":{"timestamp":" 947682126562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682128662","data":{"timestamp":" 947682128662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682131387","data":{"timestamp":" 947682131387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682133619","data":{"timestamp":" 947682133619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682136783","data":{"timestamp":" 947682136783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682139875","data":{"timestamp":" 947682139875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682142730","data":{"timestamp":" 947682142730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682144723","data":{"timestamp":" 947682144723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682146493","data":{"timestamp":" 947682146493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682148506","data":{"timestamp":" 947682148505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682155890","data":{"timestamp":" 947682155889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682157880","data":{"timestamp":" 947682157880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682160663","data":{"timestamp":" 947682160663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682162844","data":{"timestamp":" 947682162844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682165206","data":{"timestamp":" 947682165206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682166917","data":{"timestamp":" 947682166917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682169213","data":{"timestamp":" 947682169212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682172273","data":{"timestamp":" 947682172273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682174373","data":{"timestamp":" 947682174372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682176144","data":{"timestamp":" 947682176144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682179854","data":{"timestamp":" 947682179854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682182413","data":{"timestamp":" 947682182413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682185922","data":{"timestamp":" 947682185922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682191201","data":{"timestamp":" 947682191201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682193078","data":{"timestamp":" 947682193078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682195786","data":{"timestamp":" 947682195786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682198745","data":{"timestamp":" 947682198745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682203131","data":{"timestamp":" 947682203131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682205135","data":{"timestamp":" 947682205135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682207073","data":{"timestamp":" 947682207073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682210262","data":{"timestamp":" 947682210262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682212162","data":{"timestamp":" 947682212161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682220993","data":{"timestamp":" 947682220993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682223721","data":{"timestamp":" 947682223721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682226442","data":{"timestamp":" 947682226442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682229329","data":{"timestamp":" 947682229329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682232126","data":{"timestamp":" 947682232126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682234132","data":{"timestamp":" 947682234132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682236201","data":{"timestamp":" 947682236201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682238519","data":{"timestamp":" 947682238518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682241012","data":{"timestamp":" 947682241012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682243183","data":{"timestamp":" 947682243183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682245107","data":{"timestamp":" 947682245107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682247134","data":{"timestamp":" 947682247134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682249635","data":{"timestamp":" 947682249635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682252932","data":{"timestamp":" 947682252932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682254821","data":{"timestamp":" 947682254821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682257280","data":{"timestamp":" 947682257279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682259869","data":{"timestamp":" 947682259869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682263079","data":{"timestamp":" 947682263079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682265874","data":{"timestamp":" 947682265874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682268000","data":{"timestamp":" 947682268000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682271096","data":{"timestamp":" 947682271096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682273590","data":{"timestamp":" 947682273590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682275871","data":{"timestamp":" 947682275871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682278271","data":{"timestamp":" 947682278271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682280473","data":{"timestamp":" 947682280473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682283343","data":{"timestamp":" 947682283343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682286005","data":{"timestamp":" 947682286005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682288490","data":{"timestamp":" 947682288490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682290909","data":{"timestamp":" 947682290909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682292724","data":{"timestamp":" 947682292724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682295497","data":{"timestamp":" 947682295497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682298475","data":{"timestamp":" 947682298475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682301473","data":{"timestamp":" 947682301472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682304320","data":{"timestamp":" 947682304320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682305901","data":{"timestamp":" 947682305900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682309356","data":{"timestamp":" 947682309356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682311656","data":{"timestamp":" 947682311656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682313848","data":{"timestamp":" 947682313848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682315768","data":{"timestamp":" 947682315768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682318663","data":{"timestamp":" 947682318663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682322077","data":{"timestamp":" 947682322077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682325236","data":{"timestamp":" 947682325236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682327159","data":{"timestamp":" 947682327159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682329135","data":{"timestamp":" 947682329135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682331907","data":{"timestamp":" 947682331907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682333672","data":{"timestamp":" 947682333672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682335878","data":{"timestamp":" 947682335878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682337853","data":{"timestamp":" 947682337853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682342769","data":{"timestamp":" 947682342769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682344814","data":{"timestamp":" 947682344814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682347484","data":{"timestamp":" 947682347484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682350492","data":{"timestamp":" 947682350492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682352976","data":{"timestamp":" 947682352976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682355048","data":{"timestamp":" 947682355048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682356942","data":{"timestamp":" 947682356941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682359734","data":{"timestamp":" 947682359734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682362071","data":{"timestamp":" 947682362071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682363826","data":{"timestamp":" 947682363826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682365658","data":{"timestamp":" 947682365658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682367810","data":{"timestamp":" 947682367810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682371377","data":{"timestamp":" 947682371376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682373844","data":{"timestamp":" 947682373844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682378393","data":{"timestamp":" 947682378393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682380392","data":{"timestamp":" 947682380392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682382746","data":{"timestamp":" 947682382746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682385255","data":{"timestamp":" 947682385255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682387503","data":{"timestamp":" 947682387503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682389860","data":{"timestamp":" 947682389859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682391486","data":{"timestamp":" 947682391486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682393751","data":{"timestamp":" 947682393751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682398120","data":{"timestamp":" 947682398120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682401940","data":{"timestamp":" 947682401939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682403459","data":{"timestamp":" 947682403459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682408181","data":{"timestamp":" 947682408181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682410271","data":{"timestamp":" 947682410270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682413139","data":{"timestamp":" 947682413138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682416838","data":{"timestamp":" 947682416838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682420984","data":{"timestamp":" 947682420984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682422748","data":{"timestamp":" 947682422748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682426200","data":{"timestamp":" 947682426199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682429011","data":{"timestamp":" 947682429010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682431074","data":{"timestamp":" 947682431074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682433096","data":{"timestamp":" 947682433096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682435611","data":{"timestamp":" 947682435611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682439392","data":{"timestamp":" 947682439392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682441596","data":{"timestamp":" 947682441596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATATUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682443364","data":{"timestamp":" 947682443364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682447266","data":{"timestamp":" 947682447266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682449277","data":{"timestamp":" 947682449277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682449451","data":{"timestamp":" 947682449450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_152456"," gameId":" 4c260a24-8896-4aaa-9301-554a6ac17ec9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}